[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
How many more people will have to experience
the same pain we went through, Alex?
Enough, Alex.
It's already too painful.
Or maybe Mikoy is the key to bring down the whole agency.
You are the person that has been with Chiara the longest.
You're the only trainee she had.
And you are the only person who knows her.
We both know that when the two of you are facing each other,
you'll be needing that kind of courage.
What will you do, Chiara?
Kill everyone who refuses to follow you?
Of course not. That would be exhausting.
So,
it's confirmed?
It's not that simple.
Prague is Valtrovi territory.
That's where their family is strongest, and they have people everywhere.
Yup, and now that she's leading the Concordat,
her network has expanded even further.
Then we find a way she won't know about.
Mikoy.
We found her, didn't we?
It's confirmed.
What are we waiting for?
A chance that we won't all die.
So that's it?
What do you mean by that?
We found the person, didn't we?
And we're not going to do anything?
I'm not saying we're not going to do anything.
What about us?
What about all of us?
Are you the only one going?
Because the moment you authorize an operation,
the whole agency is involved.
I'm not forcing you to come.
You're not thinking like part of the team anymore.
All you care about is getting to Chiara.
Of all of us here,
I have the biggest reason to get to her,
and you know that.
What do you mean?
Mikoy, you've lost someone.
You're hurting. You're angry.
And right now,
you're letting your grief make the decisions for you.
There you go again.
You don't know how I feel.
Then stop using your concern as an excuse
for us to do nothing.
Because I don't want anything bad to happen to you.
Did I ask you to worry about me?
Mikoy, this isn't about what you're asking for.
It's my job to make sure the people with me make it home safely.
And it's our job to go after criminals.
Right?
There she is.
What are we waiting for?
-Mikoy. -Mikoy!
Mikoy.
I know I'm not your father.
And I have no intention of replacing Mario in your life.
But I've known you for a long time.
I've seen you scared.
I've seen you
make mistakes.
I've seen you fight.
And after all this time you've been with this agency,
I've come to see you as my own son.
That's why I can't just stand here and watch you like this.
I'm okay, sir.
I'm looking for justice for my father.
Bok.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
But him?
He doesn't look okay.
He's just angry.
Bok, it's not just anger.
I don't know if you've noticed.
What?
Bok.
Mikoy has changed.
He's not the Mikoy we've known all these years.
He doesn't stop training.
And he barely sleeps anymore.
His father just died.
That's why I'm worried, Bok.
He's still grieving.
That doesn't mean that--
Exactly. That's why I'm worried.
What do you mean?
Bok, I don't know if you've noticed…
Bok.
Justice?
Or are you looking for someone to take your anger out on?
We already know who killed him.
So what's the problem?
The problem is…
my conscience won't let me,
when Mario and I meet again,
just stand by and let his son follow him right away.
That's not the justice he wanted.
Dad is gone. He can't tell us what he wants anymore.
So don't use his name
to justify something that you want to do.
Bro.
What are you doing here?
Can we talk?
Go, talk to each other.
Even though he knows it could get him killed.
I won't let that happen.
Because I think Mikoy's biggest enemy right now
is no one else
but himself.
Mom?
How is she?
She's okay.
Or so she says.
What about you?
I'm okay too.
Or so you say?
Guess it runs in the family.
Bro.
We don't really get to talk anymore.
But we're talking right now.
What I mean is,
ever since Dad passed away,
it feels like we've all had our own things going on.
Mom's been busy taking care of us,
and I've been looking after Mom.
And you?
I don't know even know what you've been up to, bro.
I just have something I need to take care of.
For Dad?
For Dad.
I really miss him so much, bro.
Sometimes I even forget.
When I wake up,
I think everything's still normal.
Then,
I look for him,
wanting to talk to him.
And then I remember…
he's gone.
What about you?
Do you miss Dad?
Every day.
But I have to stay strong.
Bro, you don't have to be strong around me.
I'm your brother.
I'm so angry, Angelito.
I didn't even get to say a proper goodbye.
There was still so much I wanted to tell him…
and so much I wanted to do with him.
Me too, bro.
Bro.
Please, don't leave me too.
So what's the plan?
I've already talked to Alex.
I told her I'm a little worried about Mikoy
because I don't think he's thinking clearly anymore.
And she believed you?
I don't need her to believe me.
All I need is to give her a reason to doubt.
And the best part is,
I don't even have to lie.
Because?
Because Mikoy seems like a very unstable man,
and anyone who sees him
will believe it.
If he gets killed?
Or he has to do it himself.
It has to be his own doing.
But what about Alex?
When that happens,
that's when she'll think back to everything I told her.
Hey, hey!
Just make sure there's no evidence.
Nothing that could make anyone suspect
that someone else did it.
A brokenhearted man
and a grieving son
who just couldn't take it anymore.
It's perfect.
They'll all think the same thing.
You can't make a mistake.
Because if Chiara finds out
that we touched Mikoy…
No.
No one will ever know.
End it well.
I don't trust him.
Who?
Sianong.
We've already talked about this.
I still don't trust him.
You're not supposed to trust him.
What about you?
Do you trust him?
Mom, he's a traitor.
If he betrayed GAGO,
what assurance do we have that he won't do the same to us?
He knows what will happen to him if he does.
What if that's not enough?
What if he can't do it?
you'll do it.
The mission transfers to you, my dear.
If Sianong can't do it anymore,
you finish it.
That's why I had you trained your whole life,
to do things like this.
You can handle it.
You want me to kill Brother Mikoy?
I want you to do what you have to do.
But, Mom…
If Sianong fails,
You've been caught like this so many times,
and you still haven't learned.
You've gotten heavier.
Is that for me?
Sianong.
Bok.
Don't move.
Or I swear I'll shoot you!
So it's true.
There really is a traitor in the agency.
You?
I trusted you.
We trusted you.
Who's giving you orders?
Who are you working for?
The Concordat?
Chiara?
Carlota.
Don't talk to me.
What else is there to explain?
While I was with you,
while I trusted you,
you were just using all of us.
I didn't use you, okay?
No.
You know me.
Carlota.
We're done.
Just like that?
I don't even know what's real anymore.
Us.
We are what's real!
Carlota.
Carlota, compared to anyone else,
you're the one who knows me best.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Don't come any closer.
-I'm going to do it. -Sianong, that's enough!
Alex.
-Mikoy! -Mikoy?
Mikoy again?
Mikoy, Mikoy, Mikoy again!
Sianong, let Carlota go.
No one's going to chase you.
Let her go.
-He likes to make plans. -Sianong?
He even made a list of places he wanted to visit.
-Wait. -What?
Italy.
-Castellani. -What?!
Castellani!
Have you seen Sianong?
Ma'am, we've been here for a while, and we haven't seen him.
Agent Alex, it's open. He might come in through here.
Stay here and let us know if you see him.
Ouch!
Easy.
Where's Sianong?
-He's the mole. -Where is he?
He escaped.
How about Mikoy?
He's with Alex.
They're after him.
-Yes? -I need help. They're after me.
-And you failed! -Was that all for nothing?
This is where it ends, Sianong.